[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "What's going on here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Well, I think insecurities are feeding up on each other and although there's a sense that the problem is maybe fixable in economic sense but they may not be so fixable in a political sense.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "insecurities", "are", "feeding", "up", "on", "each", "other", "and", "although", "there", "'s", "a", "sense", "that", "the", "problem", "is", "maybe", "fixable", "in", "economic", "sense", "but", "they", "may", "not", "be", "so", "fixable", "in", "a", "political", "sense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Is that the sense you're getting?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "sense", "you", "'re", "getting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "What do you make of him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "You know, I have -- I have a fairly different take.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "have", "--", "I", "have", "a", "fairly", "different", "take", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "He says the door isn't shut now on getting back on terms diplomatically with the U.S. Do you think that's a possibility?", "question_tokens": ["He", "says", "the", "door", "is", "n't", "shut", "now", "on", "getting", "back", "on", "terms", "diplomatically", "with", "the", "U.S.", "Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "possibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "How have you managed to break down these barriers?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "managed", "to", "break", "down", "these", "barriers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I guess two things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "And, you know, he employees other female staff now, he wants to get you driving a car in Saudi Arabia, which at the moment, women can't do, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "employees", "other", "female", "staff", "now", ",", "he", "wants", "to", "get", "you", "driving", "a", "car", "in", "Saudi", "Arabia", ",", "which", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "women", "ca", "n't", "do", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Do you think the barriers are coming down fast enough?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "barriers", "are", "coming", "down", "fast", "enough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Well, I really hope they do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "really", "hope", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "In Saudi Arabia?", "question_tokens": ["In", "Saudi", "Arabia", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Have you had lessons?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "lessons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Everywhere I go.", "answer_tokens": ["Everywhere", "I", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "You drive every where else?", "question_tokens": ["You", "drive", "every", "where", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "WRB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Everywhere I go.", "answer_tokens": ["Everywhere", "I", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "The only place you can't drive a car is in your country?", "question_tokens": ["The", "only", "place", "you", "ca", "n't", "drive", "a", "car", "is", "in", "your", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "In the desert I can.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "desert", "I", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "What are the things that really frustrate you about Saudi Arabia now that you'd love to change quickly as a young woman there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "things", "that", "really", "frustrate", "you", "about", "Saudi", "Arabia", "now", "that", "you", "'d", "love", "to", "change", "quickly", "as", "a", "young", "woman", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "I wouldn't say frustrated.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "say", "frustrated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Can you appear like this on television in Saudi Arabia or would you have to be covered up?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "appear", "like", "this", "on", "television", "in", "Saudi", "Arabia", "or", "would", "you", "have", "to", "be", "covered", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "That's a tough question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "tough", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Are you impatient for that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "impatient", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "I think the whole region is impatient.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "whole", "region", "is", "impatient", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Is there a higher level of respect now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "higher", "level", "of", "respect", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "I think this generation is different than any other generation other than the fact that they're globalized and interconnected.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "this", "generation", "is", "different", "than", "any", "other", "generation", "other", "than", "the", "fact", "that", "they", "'re", "globalized", "and", "interconnected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "My husband?", "question_tokens": ["My", "husband", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "How did you find Bill Clinton?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "find", "Bill", "Clinton", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "L-TAWEEL: Incredible.", "answer_tokens": ["L-TAWEEL", ":", "Incredible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "President Obama?", "question_tokens": ["President", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Do you think he's a force for good for women's rights in the world?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "a", "force", "for", "good", "for", "women", "'s", "rights", "in", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "What would you like to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I was with him the whole time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "with", "him", "the", "whole", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Has it been upsetting to you as his wife?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "been", "upsetting", "to", "you", "as", "his", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "That is true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 298, "question": "You know that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Do you feel like, OK, it's worth it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "like", ",", "OK", ",", "it", "'s", "worth", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, I always -- honestly, I always feel like it's worth it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "always", "--", "honestly", ",", "I", "always", "feel", "like", "it", "'s", "worth", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["OK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "I think evil might be a little bit of strong word, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "evil", "might", "be", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "strong", "word", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "ORGAN: My initial thinking really.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "My", "initial", "thinking", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Are you a good girl in real life?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "good", "girl", "in", "real", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I'm a real mix.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "real", "mix", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["late night"]}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "I heard after the Emmy triumph on Sunday, you had a rather late night, Julianna?", "question_tokens": ["I", "heard", "after", "the", "Emmy", "triumph", "on", "Sunday", ",", "you", "had", "a", "rather", "late", "night", ",", "Julianna", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "We had a late night and I did.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "a", "late", "night", "and", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "PERSON": ["Julianna"], "TIME": ["late night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "So what does it mean to be a good wife?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "be", "a", "good", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "That's a very good question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Did you actually strike the poor man?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "actually", "strike", "the", "poor", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Would you stand by your man?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "stand", "by", "your", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I really think it would depend on the situation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "think", "it", "would", "depend", "on", "the", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "What were the memories you had of them splitting up and your life that you came I think to the United States with your mother and -- how much do you see of your father?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "memories", "you", "had", "of", "them", "splitting", "up", "and", "your", "life", "that", "you", "came", "I", "think", "to", "the", "United", "States", "with", "your", "mother", "and", "--", "how", "much", "do", "you", "see", "of", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Well, actually when I was -- when we're very little -- my parents split when I was 1.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", "when", "I", "was", "--", "when", "we", "'re", "very", "little", "--", "my", "parents", "split", "when", "I", "was", "1", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Where did you go?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "(INAUDIBLE), darling.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "darling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "You didn't?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "You didn't ever go to that nightclub in East Greenster (ph), did you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "ever", "go", "to", "that", "nightclub", "in", "East", "Greenster", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "What does that mean exactly?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "mean", "exactly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "I think people are going to find out soon enough on Sunday night on CBS.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "people", "are", "going", "to", "find", "out", "soon", "enough", "on", "Sunday", "night", "on", "CBS", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Allegations?", "question_tokens": ["Allegations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "That's what I'm hearing.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "I", "'m", "hearing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Not a glimmer?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "a", "glimmer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "I just don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "It's brilliantly written show, isn't it, with great characters?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "brilliantly", "written", "show", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "with", "great", "characters", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Absolutely brilliantly written.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "brilliantly", "written", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Why don't you like the whole social network thing?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "like", "the", "whole", "social", "network", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "It's not that I don't like it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "that", "I", "do", "n't", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "He took everybody down with it, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "took", "everybody", "down", "with", "it", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I enjoyed it as well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "enjoyed", "it", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Isn't there a drunk Tweeting danger?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "there", "a", "drunk", "Tweeting", "danger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I think there's even worse dangers than that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "even", "worse", "dangers", "than", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Never follow an ex girlfriend would be definitely top of the list, I think, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "follow", "an", "ex", "girlfriend", "would", "be", "definitely", "top", "of", "the", "list", ",", "I", "think", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Are you as pathetically unlucky in love in real life as you are on-screen?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "as", "pathetically", "unlucky", "in", "love", "in", "real", "life", "as", "you", "are", "on-screen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Actually, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "What's wrong with him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "wrong", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I know, exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", ",", "exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Will Gardner"]}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Real life, things are a lot happier?", "question_tokens": ["Real", "life", ",", "things", "are", "a", "lot", "happier", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Things are much better for me than Will Gardner, as far as his emotional life.", "answer_tokens": ["Things", "are", "much", "better", "for", "me", "than", "Will", "Gardner", ",", "as", "far", "as", "his", "emotional", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sophie"]}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Is she comfortable with these steamy love scenes that you're about to unfurl on the nation?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "comfortable", "with", "these", "steamy", "love", "scenes", "that", "you", "'re", "about", "to", "unfurl", "on", "the", "nation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "My girlfriend, Sophie, is not only comfortable with it.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "girlfriend", ",", "Sophie", ",", "is", "not", "only", "comfortable", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Your husband, you banned from watching?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "husband", ",", "you", "banned", "from", "watching", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I think you're holding something against her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "holding", "something", "against", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "I'm what?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Alicia.", "answer_tokens": ["Alicia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "You, unless I'm wrong, were once quoted as saying \"I don't believe monogamy is feasible\" and I've been married to a woman and to a man?", "question_tokens": ["You", ",", "unless", "I", "'m", "wrong", ",", "were", "once", "quoted", "as", "saying", "``", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "monogamy", "is", "feasible", "''", "and", "I", "'ve", "been", "married", "to", "a", "woman", "and", "to", "a", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "VBZ", "JJ", "''", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Not at the same time, though.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "the", "same", "time", ",", "though", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "There's a glittering example sitting right next to you?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "glittering", "example", "sitting", "right", "next", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "As man, I didn't feel my gender is particularly attuned to be monogamous.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "man", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "feel", "my", "gender", "is", "particularly", "attuned", "to", "be", "monogamous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Like what?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Like betraying them in friendship or betraying their trust.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "betraying", "them", "in", "friendship", "or", "betraying", "their", "trust", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"]}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Christine?", "question_tokens": ["Christine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "I think a big factor is when you have children and you're raising a family, staying together, I think the greatest gift Matthew and I gave our kids was staying together and working things out.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "big", "factor", "is", "when", "you", "have", "children", "and", "you", "'re", "raising", "a", "family", ",", "staying", "together", ",", "I", "think", "the", "greatest", "gift", "Matthew", "and", "I", "gave", "our", "kids", "was", "staying", "together", "and", "working", "things", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Do you understand how her character then would stand by her man?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "how", "her", "character", "then", "would", "stand", "by", "her", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "JJR", "RB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "He hasn't got any TV show?", "question_tokens": ["He", "has", "n't", "got", "any", "TV", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "I think that must be awful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "must", "be", "awful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "Do you think he's inherently an evil person?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "inherently", "an", "evil", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Wouldn't he, in the end, do anything for political gain?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "he", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "do", "anything", "for", "political", "gain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Does he have a moral compass, though?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "have", "a", "moral", "compass", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What would you like to know, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "to", "know", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "After you lost --", "answer_tokens": ["After", "you", "lost", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Are you sure now you're on the right side of the fence?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "sure", "now", "you", "'re", "on", "the", "right", "side", "of", "the", "fence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "What do you think of all these politicians, talking of politics, who on the Tea Party side of the Republicans, are coming out and saying same-sex marriage is disgusting and can't happen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "all", "these", "politicians", ",", "talking", "of", "politics", ",", "who", "on", "the", "Tea", "Party", "side", "of", "the", "Republicans", ",", "are", "coming", "out", "and", "saying", "same-sex", "marriage", "is", "disgusting", "and", "ca", "n't", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Well, I think if -- I think, you know, there's such -- America's this country full of such hatred in terms of politics.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "if", "--", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "such", "--", "America", "'s", "this", "country", "full", "of", "such", "hatred", "in", "terms", "of", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "Well, they have to come out of the hotel room, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "have", "to", "come", "out", "of", "the", "hotel", "room", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "Have you ever done that?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "He is not going to waste that kind of money is my sense, not his character.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "not", "going", "to", "waste", "that", "kind", "of", "money", "is", "my", "sense", ",", "not", "his", "character", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT"], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Have you all seen the first episode?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "all", "seen", "the", "first", "episode", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "No", "answer_tokens": ["No"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"]}, "docId": "110922pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "Do you all get together for a \"Good Wife\" party?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "all", "get", "together", "for", "a", "``", "Good", "Wife", "''", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "See it Sunday.", "answer_tokens": ["See", "it", "Sunday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]